Herman A. Gray Papers 5224
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Report of Unemployment Insurance State Advisory Council to the Governor and Legislature of the State of New York on the Subject of Merit Rating Pursuant to Section 518-4 of the Labor Law, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  April 10, 1939. Copy 2.
- Report of the New York Unemployment Insurance State Advisory Council on the Subject of Experience Rating Prusuant to Section 518.4 of the Labor Law in Two Parts: Part One, Conclusions and Recommendations, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  March 1. 1940.
- Report of the New York Unemployment Insurance State Advisory Council on the Subject of Experience Rating Prusuant to Section 518.4 of the Labor Law in Two Parts: Part One, Materials Pertaining to the Problem of Experience Rating, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Report of the New York State Unemployment Insurance Advisory Board on Collections and Delinquencies, 1943 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  October 5, 1943.
- Postwar Impact on Unemployment Insurance, 1944 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  March 1, 1944. A Report by the New York Unemployment State Advisory Council. 3 copies.
- Rules and Regulations of the Industrial Commissioner and Adminstrative Interpretations under the Unemployment Insurance Law, 1944 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  June 5, 1944. File no.A-620-19. Edward Corsi, Industrial Commissioner.
- New York State Unemployment Insurance Law, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  Article 18 of the New York State Labor Law as Amended by the Legislature in the Regular 1945 Session.
- Organization and Operation of the New York City Offices Volume I: Manhattan Industrial Office, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  April 1949. Local Office 610. pp.1-172 (there are no pages 173-199)
- Organization and Operation of the New York City Offices Volume I: Brooklyn Industrial Office, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  April 1949. Local Office 630. pp.200-373 (there are no pages 374-399)
- Organization and Operation of the New York City Offices Volume I: Queens Industrial Office, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  April 1949. Local Office 650. pp.400-564 (there are no pages 565-599)
- Organization and Operation of the New York City Offices Volume I: Manhattan Needle Trades Office, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  April 1949. Local Office 710. pp.600-768 (there are no pages 769-799)
- Organization and Operation of the New York City Offices Volume I: Brooklyn Needle Trades Office, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  April 1949. Local Office 730. pp.800-965 (there are no pages 969-999)
- Organization and Operation of the New York City Offices Volume I: Shipbuilding Trades Office, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  April 1949. Local Office 415. pp.1000-1164 (there are no pages 1165-1199)
- Organization and Operation of the New York City Offices Volume II: Commercial and Professional Office, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  April 1949. Local Office 115. pp.1200-1363 (there are no pages 1364-1399)
- Organization and Operation of the New York City Offices Volume II: Sales Placement Office, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  April 1949. Local Office 112. pp.1400-1565 (there are no pages 1566-1599)
- Organization and Operation of the New York City Offices Volume II:Seervice Industries Office, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  April 1949. Local Office 200. pp.1600-1769 (there are no pages 1770-1799)
- Organization and Operation of the New York City Offices Volume II: Household Office, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  April 1949. Local Office 300. pp.1800-1926 (there are no pages 1927-1999)
- Organization and Operation of the New York City Offices Volume II: Staten Island Office, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  April 1949. Local Office 550. pp.2000-2164
- I: The Reception Process, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  April 1949. Local Offices 610; 630; 650; 710; 730; 415; 115; 112; 200; 300; 550
- II: The Application Process, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- III: The Placement Process, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- IV: Counseling, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- V: Selective Placement of Handicapped, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 29)
- VI: Employer Visiting and Promotion, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 30)
- VIIA: Relations Between Insurance Offices and Employement Services, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  April 1949. Local Offices 610; 630; 650; 710; 730; 415; 115; 112; 200; 550
- VII: Relations Between Insurance Offices and Employement Services, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  April 1949. Local Offices 524; 537; 544. 2 copies.
- VIII: Labor Union Relations, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 33)
- Office Managers' Overall Statements, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 34)
- A Description of the Functions and Organization of the Office of the Metropolitan Director of the Employment Service, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  May 1949. State of New York, Department of Labor, Division of Placement and Unemployment Insurance.
- A Description of the Functions and Organization of the Office of the Director of the New York State Employment Service, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  June 1949. State of New York, Department of Labor, Division of Placement and Unemployment Insurance. 2 copies.
- Emplyment Security Operations in New York City, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  September 1, 1949. Report of the Committee on Recommendations Resulting From Survey of Employment Security Operations in New York City. State of New York, Department of Labor, Division of Placement and Unemployment Insurance.
- Availability For Work: The Status of the New York Unemployment Insurance Law and Present Practices, 1951 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  October 1951. State of New York, Department of Labor, Division of Placement and Unemployment Insurance.
- Legislative Studies, 1950-1951 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  State of New York, Department of Labor, Division of Placement and Unemployment Insurance.